<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>

    <template id="7md_website.terms_and_condition_7md" name="Terms and Conditions">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <section class="privacy-policy-container">
                <div class="container">
                    <div class="">
                        <h3 style="margin-bottom:10px;">
                            <span style="text-decoration: underline;">
                                <strong>TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF SALE :</strong>
                            </span>
                        </h3>
                        <p>This page sets out the legal terms and conditions (Terms &amp;
                            Conditions) under which 7md Store or its relevant affiliated company in
                            your territory of residence sell any of the products (Products) listed
                            on this website (Website) to you. We seek to comply with international
                            standards in distance-selling and e-commerce at all times and if you
                            have any concerns, please contact us through this website<a
                                href="/contact-us" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">
                            www.7md.ae/contact-us</a></p>
                        <p></p>
                        <h3 style="margin-bottom:10px;">
                            <span style="text-decoration: underline;">
                                <strong>Placing Your Order :</strong>
                            </span>
                        </h3>
                        <p>By placing an order for Products through our Website, you are confirming
                            that you intend to enter into a contract with us for the purchase of
                            those Products.</p>
                        <p>You place the order for your Products on the Website by clicking the
                            Confirm Order button at the end of the checkout process.</p>
                        <p>During the checkout process, you will be asked to complete your payment
                            details.</p>
                        <p>All fields indicated as compulsory must be completed (which includes
                            providing us with a valid phone number email address).</p>
                        <p>We will then send you an email confirming receipt, the details of your
                            order and the delivery costs which will be added to the purchase price
                            (if applicable).</p>
                        <h3></h3>
                        <h3 style="margin-bottom:10px;">
                            <span style="text-decoration: underline;">Note :</span>
                        </h3>
                        <p>- Neither completion of the online checkout process nor our confirmatory
                            email constitute our acceptance of your order. Our acceptance of your
                            order will take place only upon receipt of full payment from you. </p>
                        <p>- You can review the orders you have placed and their current status at
                            any time by visiting our Website and clicking on Log In at the top of
                            the page followed by selecting Track Your Order.</p>
                        <p>- If we cannot supply you with the Products you ordered for whatever
                            reason, we will not process your order and will inform you of this. If
                            you have already paid for the Products we will provide you with a full
                            refund as soon as reasonably possible.</p>
                        <p></p>
                        <h3 style="margin-bottom:10px;">
                            <span style="text-decoration: underline;">
                                <strong>Delivery / Collection :</strong>
                            </span>
                        </h3>
                        <p></p>
                        <p>- You will be asked to choose a designated store which is convenient for
                            you. Note that you may only collect from a designated store of the same
                            brand as the Products being purchased.</p>
                        <p></p>
                        <p>- If you opt for delivery, please note that delivery charges and
                            timescales vary depending on the type of Products ordered, the service
                            you select and the delivery address.</p>
                        <p></p>
                        <p>- We will try our best to either deliver the Products to your address by
                            the estimated delivery date set out in our order confirmation email. </p>
                        <p></p>
                        <p>- If we are unable to meet our estimated delivery date, we will contact
                            you as soon as we can with a revised estimated date. We will inform you
                            when the order is ready for collection or has been delivered to your
                            address, as the case may be.</p>
                        <p></p>
                        <p>- If you have selected delivery to your address and no one is available
                            at the specified address at the time of delivery, our delivery company
                            will contact you to arrange re-delivery. The Products will only be left
                            with a third party (such as building caretaker or a maid) with your
                            express authority.</p>
                        <p></p>
                        <p>- All risk in the Products you order (including risk of loss and/or
                            damage to the products) shall pass to you when they are delivered to the
                            delivery address specified in your order.<span
                                class="Apple-converted-space"></span></p>
                        <p></p>
                        <p>- Occasionally, the supply of your Products may be delayed or prevented
                            for reasons beyond our control (e.g. material shortages, import delays
                            or higher than anticipated demand). Where this is the case, we will make
                            every effort to keep you informed but shall be under no liability to you
                            for such delay or failure.</p>
                        <p></p>
                        <h3 style="margin-bottom:10px;">
                            <span style="text-decoration: underline;">
                                <strong>Cancellation, Returns, Refunds &amp; Exchanges :</strong>
                            </span>
                        </h3>
                        <p>If you wish to cancel your order, you may communicate with our Customer
                            Services department during working hours and within one hour of having
                            placed it.</p>
                        <p></p>
                        <h3 style="margin-bottom:10px;">
                            <span style="text-decoration: underline;">Note :</span>
                        </h3>
                        <p></p>
                        <p>- we cannot accept cancellations outside of these periods as the order
                            will have been processed and can only then be cancelled through our
                            returns/refunds process.</p>
                        <p></p>
                        <p>- If you paid by credit card or debit card, and you have cancelled in
                            accordance with this clause then we will reverse the authorisation or
                            process a refund transaction (as the case may be) as soon as possible
                            but we are not responsible for how long this will take to be reflected
                            on your account.</p>
                        <p></p>
                        <p>- If you wish to return your order for a refund or to exchange certain
                            Products, you must inform us within 15 days of receipt of your order and
                            in the same condition as supplied, in their original packaging with a
                            copy of the relevant invoice.</p>
                        <p></p>
                        <p>- Any items which had been provided free-of-charge with the relevant
                            Products must also be returned.</p>
                        <p></p>
                        <p>- Subject to the below exclusions, where you return your order or wish to
                            exchange certain Products, we will process a refund upon receipt of the
                            returned/exchanged Products, excluding any delivery charges you paid
                            for. For an exchange, either you will need to place a new order for
                            delivery.</p>
                        <p></p>
                        <p>- In the case of faulty, damaged or incorrectly supplied goods, we may
                            offer you a substitute or replacement Product or we will give you a full
                            refund, including any delivery charges you paid for. In any case you
                            must return the faulty, damaged or incorrect Products to us as soon as
                            possible.</p>
                        <p></p>
                        <p>- You must take reasonable care of any Products that you wish to return
                            and not use them. We will not be responsible for any loss or damage
                            caused to the items during your possession.</p>
                        <p></p>
                        <h3 style="margin-bottom:10px;">
                            <span style="text-decoration: underline;">
                                <strong>Refund Process for the Rest of the World :</strong>
                            </span>
                        </h3>
                        <p></p>
                        <p><strong>1)</strong> Youll have to cover postal charges yourself, so make
                            sure to mark your parcel as returned goods to avoid being charged
                            additional duties.</p>
                        <p></p>
                        <p><strong>2)</strong> Dont forget to ask for a tracking ID/proof of
                            shipping to track your parcel and to have proof that youve sent it.</p>
                        <p></p>
                        <p><strong>3)</strong> Once you have returned the items, it can take up to
                            28 working days maximum for us to receive the shipment and process the
                            refund.</p>
                        <p></p>
                        <p><strong>4)</strong> The amount would be refunded back to you by cash on
                            delivery return package after Aramex get to do full check on the items
                            or the card used for payment based on your selection while returning the
                            items.</p>
                        <p></p>
                        <p><strong>5)</strong> You can check with your bank after this time or Drop
                            them off at the nearest Aramex branch immediately after creating your
                            Size change request. If we dont receive the original items within 2
                            weeksof your request, well have to cancel your request to swap your
                            size.</p>
                        <p></p>
                        <p><strong>6)</strong> Exchange can only be made within 28 daysfrom the date
                            of delivery.</p>
                        <p></p>
                        <p><strong>7)</strong> It should also be in the same brand box you received.</p>
                        <p></p>
                        <p><strong>8)</strong> Item should be in a good condition and not used along
                            with the original tag and a copy of the bill.</p>
                        <p></p>
                        <p><strong>9) </strong>Once the items have been picked up and reach our
                            warehouse we will contact you with an update then you can be able to
                            purchase our products through our website: <a href="/shop/"
                                target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">www.7md.ae/shop/</a></p>
                        <p></p>
                        <p></p>
                        <p>
                            <img style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"
                                src="/7md_website/static/src/images/term-and-condition.jpeg"
                                alt="" width="973" height="688" />
                        </p>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </section>
        </t>
    </template>

</odoo>